Born

July 12th, 1993 Baku, Azerbaijan Address

M. Sharifli str., Nizami dist. AZ 1142, Baku, Azerbaijan

Contact

+994 70 200 87 14 nijatsafarli@gmail.com









Graphic

Almost 6 years I have always been curious to find an approptiate design solutions for businesses. Oil, construction, electronics, banking, software and other various industries; all businesses need a good taste of design in order to develop and expand. And that is a great pleasure to get an opportunity to impact this process with my experience and skills.

It all started with drawing. Firstly it was a hobby, then it turned to a professional pleasure. And now, as an illustrator, I put this skill into the almost every projects and created individual style in the all design solutions. On the other hands, it is still professional hobby and additional desired skill for companies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PLANHAT LLC

[Customer Success Software Platform]

Sweden / Full-time remote work January 2022 - Present

Digital Designer

- Creating all design creatives of company
- Creating visual concepts of documents, e-books and catalogues
- Re-shaping design structure of company • Creating web illustrations for website and application
- Designing webinar and podcast visuals

AZDIZAYN GROUP LLC

[Construction materials' stores network] June 2021 – January 2022

Design Manager

- Leading and managing of design and creative team
- Managing all indoor, social and outdoor design projects
- Administrating finances for design projects by given budget Participation in the recruitment and orientation of marketing
- and sales departments' new members
- Setting design standarts for chain of stores and providing them with marketing and promo materials

AZERBAIJAN NATIONAL ANTI-DOPING AGENCY (AMADA) [Govermental sport inspection organisation]

June 2020 - June 2021

Design Manager

- Manage and create all design creatives of company
- Creating visual concepts of events and conferences
- · Leading photographes&videographes shooting and finalizing products with them
- Creating educational anti-doping materials, such as, flyers, presentations, handbooks, social media posters and etc.
- Participating in departmental strategic planning Creating annual report catalogue by unique concepts

ATL CONSULTING LLC [360° marketing service- Advertisement company]

May 2019 - June 2020

Graphic Designer

- Presenting the briefs and concepts based on the client's needs and vision
- · Working with copywriter and creative director to produce final design
- · Creating visual concepts in line with the customer's needs
- Providing graphic images, illustrations, motion videos, retouched images, web designs, print materials, mockups and sketches
- Participating in departmental strategic planning

BAKU ELECTRONICS LLC [Chain of the biggest electronics household product stores]

May 2018 - March 2019

Graphic Designer

- Creating social media image and video visuals
- Designing print materials, e-books, catalogues, billboards, promo materials, flyer and posters based on campaigns or creative directions Creating key visuals for sale campaigns and adapting
 - it to various layouts and also to HTML5 banners

TECHNOL LLC [First motor oil company in Caucasus]

May 2017 - May 2018

Graphic Designer

- Conceptualizing visuals based on creative directions • Thinking creatively to produce new ideas and concepts
- and developing interactive design Creating daily social media images, GIFs and videos
- Design product labels and preparing them ready for print

FREELANCE WORK EXPERIENCE Feburary 2016 - Present

Freelance works have always been an opportunity to enter a different business fields. Besides permanent job freelancing is

a great way of enlarging portfolio with different kind of projects and companies.

Baku

Electronics



Technol



KargoFly



expressbank









EDUCATION

Business Administration & Management

BSc Business Administration

Erasmus Exchange Programme

2011-2015

Tartu University Estonia, Tartu

Turkey, Antalya

Akdeniz University

January 2014 - July 2014

DESIGN SKILLS

Azerbaijan / Native

Turkish / Native

English / Advanced

Russian / Elementary

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Adobe InDesign **Adobe After Effects** Corel Draw Suit Adobe XD Figma Blender Google Web Designer

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

SOFTWARE KNOWLEDGE

Pencil drawing Graphic Design **Art Direction Background Design**

Illustration

3D knowledge

Motion Design

Web Design

Video Editing

OTHER SKILLS

Branding

2D Traditional Art Character Design



Communication skills

Creative thinking

Full Management ability

Fully/Part-time working

Innovative approach

Analytic solving



Availibility to travel

Extensive experience with computer software&hardware





SOCIAL MEDIA PROFILES

/ Nicat Seferli



/nijatsafarli

/ Nijat Safarli

Digital Pen

Nijat Safarli

www.nijatsafarli.com Last updated in May 2022